cpvmediatraffic.com 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

In CPVMediaTraffic.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (see this article to learn more about the Privacy Policy.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by CpaMediaPublisher.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, CPVMediaTraffic.com makes use of log files. The information contained in these files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), date and time, pages referring / exit, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

****CPVMediaTraffic.com uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on the type of browser visitors or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART cookie**

Google, as vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CPVMediaTraffic.com. Of Google’s use of the DART cookie allows you to serve ads to users based on their visit to CPVMediaTraffic.com and other websites.

Users can opt for the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and privacy of the network in terms of content at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

These servers of third party advertising or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on CpaMediaPublisher.com sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by ad networks, third party to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content you see.

CPVMediaTraffic.com has no access or control over these cookies that are used by advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these ad servers from sessions for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions on how to unsubscribe from certain practices. CPVMediaTraffic.com ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and can not control the activities of other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information on managing cookies in web browsers can be found on websites of the respective browsers.

In CPVMediaTraffic.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (see this article to learn more about the Privacy Policy.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by CPVMediaTraffic.com and how it is used. Register all files Like many other Web sites, CPVMediaTraffic.com makes use of log files. The information contained in these files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), date and time, pages referring / exit, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses and other information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. Beacons CPVMediaTraffic.com Cookies and Web uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on the pages you access users or visit, customize Web page content based on the type of browser visitors or any other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART cookie**

Google, as vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CPVMediaTraffic.com. Of Google’s use of the DART cookie allows you to serve ads to users based on their visit to other sites CPVMediaTraffic.com Internet. The users can choose the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and privacy of the network in terms of content at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. These ad servers or third party ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on CPVMediaTraffic.com sent directly to your browser.

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by ad networks, third party to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content you see.CPVMediaTraffic.com has no access or control over these cookies that are used by advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these ad servers from sessions for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions on how to unsubscribe from certain practices. CPVMediaTraffic.com ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and can not control the activities of other advertisers or web sites.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information on managing cookies in web browsers can be found on websites of the respective browsers.

Welcome to CPVMediaTraffic.com. If you continue to browse and use this website you agree to abide and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern the relationship CPVMediaTraffic.com’s with you in relation to this website.

The CPVMediaTraffic.com term or “we” or “we” refers to the owner of the website. The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of our website.

**Use of this website is subject to the following conditions:**

The content of the pages on this site is for your general information and use. It is subject to change without notice.

Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or adequacy of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.

The use of any information or materials on this web site is at your own risk, for which no responsibility. It is your responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific needs.

This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but not limited to, design, design, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited except in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

All trademarks reproduced in this website which are not owned by or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.

Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and / or constitute a crime.

From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. This does not mean that we endorse the website (s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website (s).

You can not create a link to this page from another website or document without CpaMediaPublisher.com ‘s prior written consent
